# MUSSAB A. AL-TAFFAL

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

#### **PORTFOLIO**

Solution-driven Web Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer focused websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Built products for Desktop and Mobile app users meeting the highest standards of Web design, user experience, best practices and speed.



Male



+972-568166440 +971-589870686



https://www.linkedin.com/in/mussab-a-taffal/

Mussab Tafal (react-portfolio-d04o9ht3w-mussabtafals-projects.vercel.app)



April 17, 1997



mussab\_tafal@hotmail.com



Dubai, UAE.



## **EDUCATION**

- AXSOS Academy Full Stack Intensive Boot Camp.
  - Python, Java, MERN Stacks.
- AN-Najah National University.
  - **Bachelor in the Science of Engineering**



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack developer OnPassive Technologies LLC. Applications: O-Connect, OnPassive Ecosystem.

2023 - Present **Full-time Contract** 

- Design Applications as per customer request.
- Responsive Design.
- Create and manage APIs and microservices.
- API Integration.
- Database management.
- Write and maintain unit, integration, and end-to-end tests.
- Track project progress and ensure timely delivery of milestones.

**Procure Software & Logistics.** 

Full Stack developer

2022 - 2023 Freelance contract

Applications: JobPal - Job searching Platform.

- Convert Figma designs into real frontend code.
- Assist in API management and solutions.
- Fix Bugs and production issues.
- Implementing Business Logic into backend code.
- Database management.

AerData - Boeing

Software Engineer



2020 - 2022 Full-time Contract

Applications: AMS - Airplane Management System.

- Part of an engineering solution that Manages Boeing Airplanes
- Implement hands-on engineering logic to software requirements.
- Processing technical data into possible scenarios and failures.
- Database management.
- Attending Business meetings conveying client requests.
- Create test scenarios and stress tests, recreate bugs.
- Create Frontend components and document them on storybook.
- Raised the Branch coverage to 95%.
- Adhere to all required rules and code styles.
- Insure proper data transfer between all application services.

## **SKILLS**

## **Technical skills**

## **Front-End Development**

Basics: JavaScript, CSS, HTML. Frameworks: React, Angular. Tools: Bootstrap, Tailwind.

## **Back-End Development**

Language/Framework: C#: ASP.net. Language/Framework: Java: SpringBoot. Language/Framework: Python: Django, Flask.

#### **Databases**

SQL: MySQL, SQL Server, sqLITE.

NoSQL: MongoDB.

#### Soft skills

Leadership, Conflict resolution, Analysis, Decision making, Self-sufficient, fast learner.

## **CERTIFICATES**

- **Build Real-World Responsive Websites | Udemy**
- Unit Testing .Net Apps using XUnit and MOQ | Udemy
- C# Advanced fundamentals | Udemy
- **AXSOS Academy Boot camp certificate**
- Coding Dojo Boot camp | Double Black Belt
- Leadership and self-development | PCB | United States
- Leadership and conflict resolution | SOP | United States

#### **PROJECTS**

- O-Connect Video conferencing tool.
- AMS Airplane management System.
- Jobpal Job searching platform.
- Omnifoods Food ordering App
- Doctors Community Medical Form.
- Foodify Daily Meals

